I it's time to get your mouth wet with
our weekly food feature here on wake up
London we like to show you the wild and
wonderful breakfast at the Kappas or has
on offer this week we're going korean
and to food stall carrito who make
breakfast kimchi fried rice be warned
it's not for the faint-hearted the food
i'm told is hot hot hot hi I'm Dane I
work for carrito one of the pioneers in
korean street food in london at
president we offer a scrumptious
combination of korean BBQ and mexican
burrito today we're going to offer you a
delicious and hearty start to the day
and in korea unlike in the west where
you start off your breakfast with toast
cereal or pastries we like to put on a
full spread of warm rice side dishes and
soups so I'm going to show you a really
simple way that you can combine these
and have an authentic Korean starts
today we're going to make some kimchi
fried rice today so let's get fasted and
if you're feeling ambitious you can
choose to make it yourself Michelle
Obama has a great recipe on her Twitter
so maybe you'd like to follow her recipe
this is kimchi which is pickled Chinese
cabbage advocacy a few bowls of steamed
rice which is enough around two portions
and we start adding this being there
then what we get we get the courtesan
sauce now put too dang is basically like
a hot pace with a bit of sweetness to it
I'm going to put in around two
tablespoons here it just depends on how
spicy you like it mix it all together
and then while we have this going I'm
going to get a little frying pan ready
then up with olive oil we've got an egg
seeing as we're having breakfast so
cracking the egg is a sunny Friday the
yolk oozes into the rice and now I think
we'll be ready to serve up so we've got
can she still hot
this thanks PA a bit of garnish nice to
bring my new some freshness stealing
a nice spring clean facility and there
we have it simple quick easy and
delicious kimchi fried rice
you