hi my name is Sophie and today I'm going
to make him deep fried rice so one day I
was so hungry and I decided to make
kimchi fried rice because it was one of
my favorite food and it is very easy to
make so to make kimchi fried rice I use
potato onion carrot and spam it is kind
of Pam kimchi red pepper salt 1 spoon of
oyster sauce and helps below system oil
ok we have already need to make the
kimchi fried rice then let's shut the
vegetables I started diced potato onion
and carrot and Haman qg in small pieces
at this time I put them in one plate but
it was not good ideas so if you are
going to make fried rice put the
ingredients in separate plate first I
added potato and carrot because they
take time to get done and why I still
frying taro and carrot I put red pepper
because I like red pepper so if you on
your kimchi fried rice to this more
spicy then put red pepper second I put
onion well you have to still fried for
about one or two minutes and why you
still frying onions they get yellow
yellow yellow and they smell so good
then you put him and you put kimchi for
us and you surprise for one minute now
we are almost
then you put rice in the ingredients and
you put some kimchi Rickett to make the
rice more taste like kimchi then I added
oyster sauce 1 spoon of oil ourselves
don't worry too much because it gonna
get dirty and then I put some see same
way now all I have to do is still it
once again so all the ingredients are
mixed well and I put cheese on the plate
and pour the rice on the top so the
cheese are melt and it was so great
maybe because I was so hungry but it was
just so great so you should try it and
enjoy your kimchi fried rice thank you