pincus hit it Oh first back one cup of
brown onion and saute it mmm just smell
really good naughty something just a few
minutes yeah putting a little bit Brown
now add pinky that's think up something
to stir and this is a perfect meal to
take it for lunch because it has
everything in it and all you have to do
is put them in a little portion
container and it's Lily's healthy way to
eat you can also do this with the brown
rice to hear i'm adding 1 teaspoon of
meeting you don't have to put this in
which they don't have it it tastes fine
without it and I'm all of them and 1
tablespoon of soy sauce
one tsp 2 1 tablespoon of sugar with our
options okay somehow kimchi is ready to
be you may need now this is not enough
rice for you you could ask more you
asked me can go wrong with making this
there's no such a bi- how much please
pinky put in here is your choice it's
your preference if you like that of
kinky in there Sinestra and if you don't
like much kimchi but you like more rice
them so that's all right there's no
right or wrong to cook this know what
the heat up to medium but you don't want
device to get burned
this will serve four people now you can
eat this with garnish it with fried egg
it would taste good with eggs to you
smells nice now I'm going to garnish it
or add a little bit of sesame seed
that's about a tablespoon and actually
don't throw away the sauce i'm going to
add that too
so we'll be more kinky flavor
we're going to taste you see if it needs
anything else
mmm really good I'm going to add some
little bit of sesame oil now you do this
you put about a tablespoon of sesame oil
at the end to bring out the flavor and
that's poured in about mobile phone of
sesame oil okay turn off the heat and
put it in a bowl and if you want to add
a little bit more sesame seed on top to
garnish it you can do that but at home I
don't do that too much because it's just
a seating and i already put some sesame
seed but you can garnish it with a
little bit of sesame toasted sesame
seeds and it just looks pretty