hi I'm back for another cooking lesson
on lifelong windows shop today to
celebrate my promotion from sixth grade
in elementary school we're going to make
my favorite dish can you guess what it
is kimchi bokum Bob now can you open up
it's very simple and easy to make and
it's one of the most famous and popular
dishes of all my friends every time I
bring it to school my friends are like
oh please can I would buy it it looks so
good I'd like you just can't stand my
cooking so anyways that's how your
friends and your family will react if
you make my conjugal so the ingredients
are a cup of chopped kimchi kimchi sauce
rice about two slices of spam one
mushroom a quarter of the onion and
one-eighth of a zucchini the very first
step is to chop your aunt your crunch of
branch up top no I'm kidding chop it in
life first I melted chocolate zucchini
now i'm going to start chopping the
mushrooms talking mushroom and faster
chopping the delicious but yet not so
healthy spam and last i'm going to chop
onions
okay now I have all the ingredients now
I'm going to respect to the second step
is to stir fry all the ingredients now
there is a specific step that you should
follow and if you don't follow your
kimchi bokum bob is lock letter not as
good as mine so follow first hit the
slope then put Oh guys I forgot sorry
brain fork I forgot to mention all the
oil you need that for the surf by and if
you don't have audit boil you can use
other sorts of vegetable oil okay now
put two spoons of olive oil
once there ok now we got two spoons of
olive oil then we add onion the next
thing we do is to put in is spam spam
jewel hoard your dupatta with their own
announcer now you add my mother's
homemade beautiful yummy kimchi to the
pot
look at it
investing beneath the atom is mushrooms
and
okay now find the ad zucchinis now that
all the ingredients has joined the party
now is trying for the main the rice
we're almost there ok now we finally put
in
now that we've made our young and kimchi
blue kumba it's time for us to eat I
mean a starfish now on you can put other
things on the rise like eggs I'm
personally not an egg person but if you
really like eggs you can put on eggs you
can like sprinkle awesome sesame seeds
do whatever you want I'm sorry starfish
back cuz I have to take one of your mix
mmm you know this is really good song
try making your ear now it is easy to
make one to say and going to eat